ERIK SVETLIK

Self-driven full stack assistant developer with 1.5 years of experience designing, developing, and testing applications within a web-based CMMS. Passionate about building web applications with high enduser satisfaction, and continuously developing programming knowledge and skills on a personal level.

CONTACT

svetlik.erik@gmail.com 361.772.1612 eriksvetlik.github.io/portfolio

SKILLS

HTML CSS/Bootstrap JavaScript/jQuery ASP SQL VBScript

EDUCATION

HISTORY B.A.

Aug 2010 - May 2014 Texas A&M University

PROJECTS

Halo 5 Missions API Game of Thrones Quotes API Nook & Cranny Bookstore Christmas Countdown Form Validation

WORK EXPERIENCE

ASSISTANT DEVELOPER/CLIENT SUPPORT SPECIALIST AT IMPAK SOLUTIONS

Ian 2020 - Present

Full-Time

In addition to Client Support, I:

- Work in designing, coding, and testing new and current applications alongside the Senior Developer.
- Responsible for daily and weekly backups of software applications and client data using FTP software.
- Was assigned independent programming projects after 2 months of internal training.

CLIENT SUPPORT SPECIALIST AT IMPAK SOLUTIONS

Nov 2017 - Dec 2019

Full-Time

- Provided software support and software training to client users.
- Worked with Programming to perform quality assurance tests.
- Managed application requests, project plans and client feedback while providing status updates to clients and management.
- Implemented changes to achieve 91% of service requests completed on time department wide.

■ PRODUCT ANALYST AT REYNOLDS AND REYNOLDS

Oct 2015 - Nov 2017

Full-Time

- Assisted in managing and designing leading telephony product.
- Tested programming requests and programming projects for accuracy, optimal functionality, and fulfillment of requests and project goals.
- Wrote program change notices for client and internal users.

SOFTWARE IMPLEMENTATION CONSULTANT AT REYNOLDS AND REYNOLDS

May 2014 - Oct 2015

Full-Time

- Managed the set-up and training of telephony product.
- Traveled to client sites nationally to work personally with customers.